Guide to the Samuel J. Tilden papers, 1794-1886 [bulk 1835-1876]
The New York Public Library. Manuscripts and Archives Division.
- Series I. Correspondence, 1810 - 1919, n.d.; 38247; 35 boxes, 14.5 linear feet
  - I. B. General, 1830 - 1919, n.d.; 38280
    - Miller, E., undated; 39110 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Miller, George L., 1871 - 1885; 39111 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Miller, George McCullough, 1858; 39112 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Miller, Theodore, 1842, 1860 - 1874; 39113 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Mills, Roger Q., 1886; 39114 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Miller, W., 1875; 39115 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Minier, S., 1868 - 1872; 39116 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Minturn, Robert Bowne, 1871 - 1883; 39117 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Mitchell, Alexander, 1875 - 1876; 39118 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Mitchell, John W., 1846; 39119 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Money, Henry de Soto, 1876, 1880; 39120 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Montgomery, S. M., 1876; 39121 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Moody, D. L., 1885; 39122 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Moore, Eli, 1845; 39123 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Morgan, Edwin D., 1877; 39124 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Morgan, Geoge W., 1868, 1876 - 1877; 39125 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Morgan, John T., 1876; 39126 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Morgan, M., 1839; 39127 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Morgan, R. J., 1883; 39128 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Morrall, Cyrus, 1860, 1873 - 1876; 39129 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Morris, Fordham, 1874 - 1875; 39130 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Morris, Robert H., 1843; 39131 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Morris, S. D., 1876; 39132 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Morrissey, John, 1868, 1874 - 1876; 39133 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Morrison, William Ralls, 1868; 39134 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Morse, Leila, 1872, 1880 - 1881; 39135 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Morse, Samuel F.B., 1863 - 1874; 39136 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Morton, Levi Parsons, 1874; 39137 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Moses, Frederick, 1878; 39138 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Moulton, Steven D., 1846; 39139 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Murphy, E., 1874; 39140 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Murphy, Henry C., 1867 - 1875; 39141 (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Myers, T. Bailey, 1846, 1860, n.d; 39142 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - National Johnson Club, 1866; 39143 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Nelson, Samuel, 1869; 39144 (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - New York Church Extension & Missionary Society, 1875; 39145 (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - New York Law Institute, 1876 - 1877; 39146 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - New York Pilots Association, 1846; 39147 (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - New York Produce & Maritime Independent Merchants Cleveland & Hendricks Club, 1884; 39148 (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - New York Produce Exchange, 1874; 39149 (Box 18, Folder 63)
    - New York State Soldiers Depot, 1863; 39150 (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - New-York Society Library, 1839; 39151 (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Newburgh Centennial Celebration Committee, 1882; 39152 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Newell, George W., 1852 - 1861; 39153 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Newell, W. C., 1876; 39154 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Newport, H., 1879; 39155 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      Relating to Tylden genealogy.
    - Newton, John, 1876, 1886; 39156 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      See also: Coastal defense; James Carlisle, William Henry Jacques, Samuel Randall.
    - Nicholson, James B., 1870; 39157 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Nicoll, Henry, 1846, 1859; 39158 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Niles, W. W., 1875; 39159 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      See also: Canal Ring.
    - Nilsson, Christine, undated; 39160 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Nooney, Robert B., 1876; 39161 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Nordhoff, Charles, 1874, 1885; 39162 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Norris, Thomas, ca. 1866; 39163 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - North, James, 1886; 39164 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - North, Samuel, 1868 - 1875; 39165 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - North Chicago Rolling Mill Company, 1874 - 1875; 39166 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Norton, Charles B., 1861; 39167 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Nott, Eliphalet, 1852; 39168 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Oakley, Thomas J., 1846; 39169 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - O'Brien, Denis, 1880, 1883; 39170 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - O'Brien, James, 1872 - 1879; 39171 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - O'Brien, John, 1846, 1885; 39172 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - O'Conor, Charles S., 1846 - 1884, n.d.; 39173 (Box 19, Folder 22-25)
    - Ogden, William B., 1857 - 1873, 1880, n.d; 39174 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - O'Gorman, Richard, 1866, 1871; 39175 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - O'Hurley, H., 1876; 39176 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - O'Leary, T., 1879; 39177 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Olcott, Thomas W., 1832, 1846; 39178 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Olney, Peter, 1876, 1878; 39179 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - O'Meara, James, 1885 - 1886; 39180 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Orr, Alexander Ector, 1876, 1885 - 1886; 39181 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Osborn, Albert H., 1875; 39182 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Osborn, William H., 1871; 39183 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - O'Sullivan, John L., 1841 - 1884; 39184 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Otis, Eliza Proctor, 1886; 39185 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Ottendorfer, Oswald, 1872 - 1876; 39186 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Page, A. C., 1846; 39187 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Page, A. S., 1875; 39188 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Paige, David R., 1883; 39189 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Paine, N. E., 1868; 39190 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Palmer, F. A., 1871; 39191 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Palmer, G. W., 1860; 39192 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Palmer, John M., 1879; 39193 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Parker, Alton B., 1879 - 1881; 39194 (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Parker, Amasa J., 1858 - 1875; 39195 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Parker, Courtlandt, 1877 - 1878; 39196 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Parker, George F., 1878; 39197 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Parker, Joel, 1878 - 1879, 1886; 39198 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - Parker, N. W., 1874; 39199 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Parker, S. H., 1875; 39200 (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Parkhurst, Charles Henry, 1884; 39201 (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - Parmely, T. N., 1865 - 1866; 39202 (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Parmenter, Jerome B., undated; 39203 (Box 19, Folder 55)
    - Parmenter, R. A., 1881; 39204 (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - Parsons, John E., 1875 - 1876; 39205 (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - Patterson, C. Y., 1861; 39206 (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - Payne, Eloise, 1856 - 1857; 39207 (Box 19, Folder 59)
    - Payne, H. B., 1880; 39208 (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - Peaslee, Charles H., 1853; 39209 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      See also: Franklin Pierce
    - Peck, Daniel, 1832 - 1834; 39210 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Peck, George W., 1879; 39211 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      Regarding Tilden's candidacy in 1880.
    - Peck, John J., 1845, 1864, 1875; 39212 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Peckham, Rufus W. Jr., 1872 - 1874; 39213 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Peckham, Wheeler H., 1862 - 1876; 39214 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Pendleton, George H., 1868; 39215 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Pentz, Adam P., 1846; 39216 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Perkins, Eli, 1877; 39217 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Perkins, Theodore B., 1873; 39218 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Perrin, E. O., 1864; 39219 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Perry, Abner, 1834; 39220 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Peyton, J. E., 1876; 39221 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Phelps, Benjamin K., 1875; 39222 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Phelps, Charles, 1875; 39223 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Phelps, Edward J., 1869 - 1870, 1886; 39224 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Phelps, Royal, 1862 - 1876; 39225 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Phelps, William Walter, 1878; 39226 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Phillips, D. L., 1872; 39227 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Phillips, Wendell, 1881; 39228 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Pierce, Franklin, 1852 - 1857; 39229 (Box 20, Folder 21)
      See also: Charles H. Peaslee
    - Pierce, Walter, 1875; 39230 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Pierce, Winslow, 1868; 39231 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Pierrepont, Edwards, 1875 - 1885, n.d.; 39232 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Pierson, Catherine H., 1848, 1861; 39233 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Pillow, Gideon, 1876; 39234 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Pillsbury, E. F., 1868; 39235 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Pinkney, Campbell W., 1871, 1874; 39236 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Pitts, Elias, 1832 - 1844; 39237 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Pontroell, George S., 1882; 39238 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Poor, Henry V., 1863, 1869; 39239 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Porter, Andrew D., 1861; 39240 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Porter, Anthony B, 1870; 39241 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Porter, Fitzjohn, 1875; 39242 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Porter, James D., 1876; 39243 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Porter, John K., 1858 - 1882; 39244 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Potter, Clarkson, 1849, 1863 - 1881; 39245 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Potter, Eliphalet Nott, 1876; 39246 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Potter, Howard, 1871 - 1886; 39247 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Potter, O. W., 1877 - 1878; 39248 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Potter, Thomas B., 1877; 39249 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Powell, William J., ca. 1874; 39250 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Power, M. J., 1874, 1878; 39251 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Pratt, Daniel, 1874; 39252 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Prescott (first name unknown), 1836; 39253 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Preston, William, 1876 - 1885; 39254 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Priest, John G., 1882; 39255 (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Prince, Frederick, 1868, 1876 - 1877; 39256 (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Prior, James J., 1862; 39257 (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Pruyn, John V. L., 1872, 1878; 39258 (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - Pryer, Mary Margaretta, ca. 1884; 39259 (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - Pryor, Roger A., 1868; 39260 (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Pulitzer, Joseph, 1876, 1883 - 1885; 39261 (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - Purcell, William, 1871 - 1875, 1881; 39262 (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - Purdy, Elijah F., 1841 - 1845; 39263 (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - Purser, George H., 1844, 1885; 39264 (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - Putnam, L. H., 1856 - 1864; 39265 (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - Pyne, Percy R., 1882; 39266 (Box 20, Folder 58)
    - Quackenbos, N., 1880; 39267 (Box 20, Folder 59)
    - Raguet, Conde, 1840 - 1841; 39268 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Rahallo, Charles A., 1871, 1876; 39269 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Railey, Logan, 1872; 39270 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Randall, Alexander Williams, 1868; 39271 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Randall, Robert E., 1882; 39272 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Randall, Samuel J., 1845, 1868 - 1886; 39273 (Box 21, Folder 6-9)
      See also: Coastal Defense; James Carlisle, William Henry Jacques, and John Newton.
    - Randolph, Theodore F., 1868, 1875; 39274 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Ranney, Rufus W., 1862, 1869 - 1871; 39275 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Ransom, Benjamin, 1845; 39276 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Rapallo, C. H., 1864; 39277 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Raymond, C. B., 1862; 39278 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Raymond, Henry Jarvis, 1859; 39279 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Rayner, Emily L., 1878; 39280 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Read, John R., 1885; 39281 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Redfield, D. W., 1863; 39282 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Reemelin, Charles, 1885; 39283 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Reeves, Henry A., 1885; 39284 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Reid, John A., 1870; 39285 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Reid, John R., 1882; 39286 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Reid, Whitelaw, 1871 - 1878; 39287 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Reid, William B., 1863; 39288 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Reis Brown & Berger, 1875 - 1877; 39289 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Reis, George C., 1874 - 1876; 39290 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Rhett, Robert Barnwell, 1862, 1868, n.d; 39291 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Rice, R. D., 1876; 39292 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Rice, William G., 1885; 39293 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Richmond, Dean, 1857 - 1867; 39294 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Richmond, Henry A., 1866 - 1882; 39295 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Richmond, J.M., 1876 - 1878; 39296 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Ringgold, James Trapier, 1880; 39297 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Robb, James, 1862; 39298 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Robbins, Eliza, ca. 1844, n.d.; 39299 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Roberts, G. B., 1874; 39300 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Roberts, Marshall O., 1860 - 1861; 39301 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Robertson, Wyndham, 1861; 39302 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Robinson, David C., 1877 -1878; 39303 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Robinson, Edward Randolph, 1874 - 1875; 39304 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Robinson, Lucius, 1869 - 1876; 39305 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Romeyn, Theodore Bayard, 1864; 39306 (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Roosevelt, Charles, 1875; 39307 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Roosevelt, James, 1846, 1876; 39308 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Roosevelt, Robert B., 1863 - 1880; 39309 (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1863, 1872, 1876; 39310 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Root, R. C., 1853, 1858; 39311 (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - Rose, Joseph, 1856; 39312 (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - Rosecrans, William S., 1880, 1883; 39313 (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - Ross, E. P., 1876; 39314 (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - Rowley, W. C., 1866 - 1871; 39315 (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - Ruggles, William B., 1876, 1882; 39316 (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - Rush, Benjamin, 1876; 39317 (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - Russell, C. A., 1868; 39318 (Box 21, Folder 54)
    - Russell, W. F., 1879; 39319 (Box 21, Folder 55)
    - Russell, W. J., 1886; 39320 (Box 21, Folder 56)
    - Sage, Russell, 1870, 1879; 39321 (Box 21, Folder 57)
    - St. John, Daniel Bennett, 1876 - 1879; 39322 (Box 21, Folder 58)
    - Sancton, Clark, 1839; 39323 (Box 21, Folder 59)
    - Sanders, Dallas, 1886; 39324 (Box 21, Folder 60)
    - Sanders, George W., 1864; 39325 (Box 21, Folder 61)
    - Sands, Julia M., 1857, n.d.; 39326 (Box 21, Folder 62)
    - Sands, Mahlon, 1872; 39327 (Box 21, Folder 63)
    - Sands, Robert A., 1843, 1846; 39328 (Box 21, Folder 64)
    - Sarony, Otto, 1886; 39329 (Box 21, Folder 65)
    - Sayre, Lewis A., 1869, 1879; 39330 (Box 21, Folder 66)
    - Sayre, (First name unknown), undated; 39331 (Box 21, Folder 67)
    - Scanendoah, Daniel, 1875; 39332 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Schell, Augustus, 1863 - 1874; 39333 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Schell, Richard, 1866, 1871; 39334 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Scheer, Solomon, 1870; 39335 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Schofield, Glennin W., 1872; 39336 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Schoolcraft, Henry Rowe, 1846; 39337 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Schoonmaker, Augustus Jr., 1875 - 1880; 39338 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Schuey, Thomas F., 1885; 39339 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Schulte, Eduard, 1883; 39340 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Schultz, Jackson S., 1871 - 1876, n.d.; 39341 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Schurz, Karl, 1875; 39342 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Schuyler, George W., 1875 - 1876; 39343 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Schuyler, Louisa Lee, 1876; 39344 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Schuyler, S. D., 1886; 39345 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      See also: Coastal Defense; James Carlisle, John Newton, Samuel Randall.
    - Scott, John B., 1846; 39346 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Scott, Thomas A., 1863 - 1878, n.d.; 39347 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Scott, W. L., 1884; 39348 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - The Scottish American Investment Trust, 1878; 39349 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Scovel, James M. 1876 - 1885}, 39350 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Scranstone, Hiram, 1863; 39351 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Scribner, G. Hilton, 1875, undated; 39352 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Secor, Charles A., 1846, 1857; 39353 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Seeger, F., 1876; 39354 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Seguin, E. A., 1882; 39355 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Seligman, J. P., 1875; 39356 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Semple, Henry C., 1884; 39357 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Seward, Clarence A., 1869; 39358 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Seward, G. W., 1831; 39359 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Seward, Json W., 1830, 1893; 39360 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Seymour, Horatio, 1855 - 1886, n.d.; 39361 (Box 22, Folder 30-36)
    - Seymour, John T., 1864, 1875; 39362 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Shaw, Samuel M., 1876; 39363 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Shekell, Richard R., 1848; 39364 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Shelby, W. R., 1870 - 1871; 39365 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Sheldon, Edwin H., 1859; 39366 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Shepherd, Elliott F., 1870 - 1880; 39367 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Sherman, Charles B., 1832 - 1844; 39368 (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Sherman, Henry A., 1886; 39369 (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Sherman, Isaac, 1863 - 1867; 39370 (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - Sherman, John, 1866 - 1879; 39371 (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - Sherman, Roger M., 1879; 39372 (Box 22, Folder 47)
    - Sherwood, Julius, 1846; 39373 (Box 22, Folder 48)
    - Shoenberger & Blair, 1870; 39374 (Box 22, Folder 49)
    - Sibley, Hiram, 1886; 39375 (Box 22, Folder 50)
    - Sickey, Daniel E., 1846; 39376 (Box 22, Folder 51)
    - Sigourney, John M., 1868; 39377 (Box 22, Folder 52)
    - Silliman, Benjamin D., 1846, 1861 - 1879; 39378 (Box 22, Folder 53)
    - Simmons, J. Edward, 1885; 39379 (Box 22, Folder 54)
    - Sinnot, James P., 1867 - 1876; 39380 (Box 22, Folder 55)
    - Skimmer, Mark, 1863; 39381 (Box 22, Folder 56)
    - Slack, Charles W., 1881; 39382 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Slocum, Henry Warner, 1868 - 1872; 39383 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Smalley, George W., 1877; 39384 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Smith, A. J., 1876; 39385 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Smith, Alfred, 1831 - 1846; 39386 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Smith, Ballard, 1876 - 1884; 39387 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Smith, C. P., 1859; 39388 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Smith, Cabb, 1862 - 1879; 39389 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Smith, Cora E., 1880 - 1886, n.d.; 39390 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Smith, E. Delafield, 1875; 39391 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Smith, George Wilson, 39392
      - Correspondence with Daniel Manning, 1885; 39393 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence with Manton Marble, 1875 - 1876, 1884, n.d; 39394 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence with Samuel J. Tilden, 1867 - 1886, n.d.; 39395 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - Letters received, 1875 - 1886, 1908, 1919; 39396 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Telegrams relating to 1880 Democratic National Convention, 1880 Jun; 39397 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Letterpress copybook, 1870 - 1874; 39398 (Volume 1)
      - Letterpress copybook, 1874 - 1875; 39399 (Volume 2)
    - Smith, J. Lawrence, 1853; 39400 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Smith, John Cotton, 1869, 1871; 39401 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Smith, Nicholas, 1878; 39402 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Smith, Perry H. Jr. {1865 - 1885, 39403 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Smythe, H. A., 1866; 39404 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Snowden, C. A., 1882 - 1883; 39405 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Southmayd, Charles F., 1868; 39406 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Speer, Charles, 1876; 39407 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Spofford, (First name unknown), 1846; 39408 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Spriggs, J. Thomas, 1868 - 1884; 39409 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Springer, R. R., 1873; 39410 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Springer, William M., 1876 - 1885; 39411 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Starbuck, James F., 1845; 39412 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Stebbins, Charles, 1874 - 1876, n.d.; 39413 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Stebbins, Henry G., 1855, 1863, 1875; 39414 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Stephens, Stephen D. Jr., 1878; 39415 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Sterne, Simon, 1873 - 1880; 39416 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Stetson, Francis Lynde, 1871, 1874 - 1877; 39417 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Stevens, Alexander W., 1845; 39418 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Stevens, Isaac Ingalls, 1860; 39419 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Steveson, J. D., 1839, 1844 - 1845; 39420 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Stevenson, John W., 1880; 39421 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Stewart, A. T., 1875; 39422 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Stickney, Albert, 1872, 1876; 39423 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Stiles, J. W., 1846; 39424 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Stillwell, Silas M., 1860, 1875; 39425 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Stimson, H. C., 1860 - 1865; 39426 (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Stockton, John P., 1871, 1877; 39427 (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - Stokes, James, 1876; 39428 (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - Stokes, Thomas, 1874; 39429 (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - Stone, A., 1880; 39430 (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - Stone, R. G., 1866; 39431 (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - Storey, W. F., 1868, undated; 39432 (Box 23, Folder 48)
    - Stoughton, E. W., undated; 39433 (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - Stout, Francis A., 1876; 39434 (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - Stryker, Francis B., 1842; 39435 (Box 23, Folder 51)
    - Stryker, John L., 1846 - 1867, 1875; 39436 (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - Sullivan, Algernon S., 1875 - 1876; 39437 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Sullivan, T. J., 1886; 39438 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Sumner, William Graham, 1885; 39439 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Sutherland, Isaiah, 1855; 39440 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Swan, Charles H., 1873 - 1875; 39441 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Swan, Henrietta J., 1882; 39442 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Swank, James M., 1885; 39443 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Swayne, Charles, 1849; 39444 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Swayne, E. B., 1860; 39445 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Swayne, Noah Haynes, 1860 -1883; 39446 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Swayne, Wager, 1861 - 1869; 39447 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Sweat, Margaret J. M., 1883; 39448 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Sweeney, Peter B., 1860 - 1870; 39449 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Sweet, S. H., 1875; 39450 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Sykes, Martin, L., 1877 - 1884; 39451 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Taintor, Henry Fox, 1872 - 1877; 39452 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Tallmadge, Nathaniel P., 1845; 39453 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - The Tammany Society, 1838 - 1876; 39454 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Tapley, John, 1884; 39455 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Taylor, Alfred H., 1875 - 1876; 39456 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Taylor, Douglas, 1866 - 1868, 1885 - 1886; 39457 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Taylor, John, 1855; 39458 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Taylor, John J., 1863, 1872 - 1876; 39459 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Taylor, Moses, 1840; 39460 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Taylor, R., 1876, n.d.; 39461 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Terry, Edmond, 1846; 39462 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Thatcher, Thomas A., 1882; 39463 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Thayer, J. S., undated; 39464 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Thomas, P. H., 1839 - 1840; 39465 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Thompson, George S., 1876; 39466 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Thompson, H. O., 1879; 39467 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Thompson, J. Edgar, 1864 - 1869; 39468 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Thompson, Jonathan, 1840; 39469 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Thompson, John G., 1876 - 1885; 39470 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Thorn, Owen, 1866; 39471 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Thornhill, Thomas L., 1875; 39472 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Thrasher, John Sidney, 1860; 39473 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Throop, Charlotte W., 1886; 39474 (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Throop, Montgomery H., 1875; 39475 (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Thurber, Horace K., 1875; 39476 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Thurman, Allen G., 1863 - 1876; 39477 (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Thurston, A. S., 1855; 39478 (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Thurston, C. B., 1859; 39479 (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Thurstone, William, 1874; 39480 (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Tiemann, Daniel F., 1859, 1871; 39481 (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - Timby, Theodore, Ruggles, 1886; 39482 (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - Titus, James H., 1846, 1876; 39483 (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - Tobey. F. W., 1875; 39484 (Box 24, Folder 48)
    - Townsend, Dwight, 1868, 1875 - 1878; 39485 (Box 24, Folder 49)
    - Townsend, Franklin, 1875; 39486 (Box 24, Folder 50)
    - Townsend, George Alfred, 1875; 39487 (Box 24, Folder 51)
    - Townsend, Thomas S., 1875; 39488 (Box 24, Folder 52)
    - Tracey, E.H., 1859; 39489 (Box 24, Folder 53)
    - Tracey, James F., 1881; 39490 (Box 24, Folder 54)
    - Tracy, Charles, 1877; 39491 (Box 24, Folder 55)
    - Train, George Francis, undated; 39492 (Box 24, Folder 56)
    - Tremain, Alva H., 1874; 39493 (Box 24, Folder 57)
    - Tremain, Lyman, 1863; 39494 (Box 24, Folder 58)
    - Trevor, John Bond, 1876 - 1886; 39495 (Box 24, Folder 59)